My name is Mike Degen.
I’m 46.
My Manulife Vitality age is 45,
and I’ve been a member for 8 years.
Initially, I was looking
for life insurance.
Through word of mouth,
we found the Manulife Vitality product.
I discovered that Manulife Vitality
wasn’t just life insurance.
It had gamification built into it,
where my weekly reward points
could give me a points tally.
It could give me opportunities
to win gift cards.
And that became fun,
and later on, important.
What might start with a walk for me
to get my active rewards
is now turned into a walk run.
Those walk runs have turned
into all-out runs,
So, it becomes a little bit less
about the program
and more about how I’m getting
the benefits out of it.
This is all stemming
from just life insurance,
which I think is kind of crazy
to think about how life insurance
has made me more active
and made me choose healthier choices.
Would I recommend
the Manulife Vitality product?
I would 100% recommend it.
It became just a way of life,
a lifestyle change.
Healthier choices became organic
just as a result of just being
held accountable and
wanting to do it for what started out
at first the product,
but then for myself
and then for my family.